[
  {
    "front": "book",
    "back": "das Buch",
    "info": "nice word"
  },
  {
    "front": "keyboard",
    "back": "die Tastatur",
    "info": ""
  },
  {
    "front": "lamp",
    "back": "die Lampe",
    "info": ""
  },
  {
    "front": "magazine",
    "back": "die Zeitschrift",
    "info": ""
  },
  {
    "front": "bike",
    "back": "das Fahrrad",
    "info": "also velo"
  },
  {
    "front": "kitchen",
    "back": "die KÃ¼che",
    "info": ""
  },
  {
    "front": "computer",
    "back": "der Rechner",
    "info": ""
  },
  {
    "front": "sink",
    "back": "das Waschbecken",
    "info": "hard word"
  },
  {
    "front": "note",
    "back": "das Zettel",
    "info": "useful word"
  },
  {
    "front": "scissors",
    "back": "die Schere",
    "info": "ok"
  }
]